Guide to the William R. George family papers, 1750-1989.
George, William R. family papers, 1750-1989.
- Series II. Manuscripts
  - Term papers, articles and speeches about G.J.R.:
    - "Self-Governing Teenage Community Helps Make Better U.S. Citizens", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - "Social Hospital and Social Sanitarium", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - "Treatment versus Punishment by Means of Social Clinic", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - "The G.J.R.", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - untitled regarding election of Harrison Appleby as G.J.R. president, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - fragments about G.J.R., n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Fragments about G.J.R., n.d. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Phalanx material, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 4-5)
  - Articles about other junior republics and junior republic movement:
    - Freeborn, Malcolm J.: "Plans for a Large Scale Method of Democratic Training for Youth.", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Gates, Rev. L.S.: "A Self-governing Orphanage in India.", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Heindel, Ned D.: "Redington and the Carter Junior Republic.", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - McCormick, Anna: "The School City.", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - See, Alonzo B.: "Child Labor Laws.", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Stowe, Lyman B.: "Self-Government.", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - No author cited: "The Junior, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Municipality"; "The Junior Republic Movement.", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Notes about collection and G.J.R. history; most by Edith Freeborn, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Sale of George property, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Building Fund; notebook with lists of contributors, cancelled checks, "Manual of Information for Board of Directors of the G.J.R. Association, Inc.", 1939-1947 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Building Fund; clippings, printed booklet "A Message for Founders Day," carbon copy lists of contributors, carbon copy "Report of Treasurer of G.J.R. Alumni 50th Anniversary Fund," handwritten notes, correspondence, typescript notes, typed excerpts from diary of Esther George, carbon copy list of people attending Founders Day, cover from printed donation coupon book, postcard, minutes from meeting of G.J.R. Alumni Association Memorial Government Building Fund Committee, 1936-1960 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Building Fund; typescript statement by Edith Freeborn, typescript and handwritten notes, carbon copy of report by M. Freeborn on building fund, 1961-1968 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Building Fund; printed leaflets, correspondence, carbon copy list of Board of Directors, handwritten and typescript excerpts from minutes of Board of Directors meetings, carbon copy list of ex-citizens and helpers, Founders Day printed program, printed invitation, carbon copy minutes of Alumni meeting, clipping, J.M. McDonald Foundation Annual Reports (1965, 1966)., 1946-1966 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Minutes of meeting of Board of Directors, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Series III. Bound Volumes - Manuscripts
  - Diary kept by William R. George, 1881 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Diary kept by William R. George, 1897 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Diary kept by William R. George, 1898 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
  - Diary kept by Miss Cross for G.J.R. library, 1899-1900 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Diary kept by Esther George on trip to California, 1907 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Friendship calendar by J.E. "Sister Nellie" Hurley, 1914 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Diary kept by William R. George, 1920 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Diary kept by citizen E.R. Alton, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1941 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1942 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1943 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1944 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1945 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1958 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Diary kept by Esther George, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Memo book, 1889 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - "List of Things Stored" for Fresh Air Camp, 1891 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Memo book kept by William R. George, 1896-1897 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Memo book, 1898-1904 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Memo book kept by William R. George, 1900-1901 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Memo book kept by William R. George, 1909 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Itinerary of speaking engagements of William R. George, 1910-1914 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Memo book kept by William R. George, 1935-1936 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - "List of calls and flowers to Mother" by Edith George Freeborn, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Three small memo books kept by William R. George., n.d. (Box 61, Folder 10-12)
  - Two military muster books by William R. George., n.d. (Box 61, Folder 13-14)
  - Lists of letters, kept by Esther George, 1895-1897 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Lists of letters, kept by Esther George, 1897 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Lists of letters, kept by Esther George, 1916 (Box 61, Folder 17-18)
  - Lists of letters, kept by Esther George during hospital stay of William R. George., 1929 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - List of Christmas cards, kept by Esther George, 1930-1941 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - List of Christmas cards, kept by Esther George and Edith Freeborn, 1941-1976 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Definitions of words kept by William R. George, 1896-1897 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous volume about G.J.R., by William R. George, 1919 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Quotations, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Book draft (?) by William R. George, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Account book for jewelry box business of William R. George, 1886-1887 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Fresh Air Account, ca.1890 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Account book for eggs, butter, and coffee., 1893-1895 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - G.J.R. household accounts, 1895 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Account book kept by Eleanor B. George, records of payments, 1898-1899 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - G.J.R. Association account book, 1901-1916 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Loose bills, 1902-1915 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Account book kept by William R. George, 1913-1916 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Cancelled checks written by William R. George., 1913-1930 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Account book kept by William R. George, 1917-1920 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Savings passbook for William R. George Memorial (Building) Fund, 1938-1950 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Steno notebook by William R. George, ca.1900 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Notebook with subject matter of Citizens Made and Remade., 1910 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Steno notebook by William R. George, 1910 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Steno notebook by William R. George, 1910-1912 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Notebook of "Daddy's Bulletins.", 1911 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Steno notebook by William R. George, 1917 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Steno notebooks by William R. George, 1920 (Box 63, Folder 7-10)
  - Steno notebook by William R. George, 1921 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Notebook by William R. George - "Idea of Junior Republic Representatives in Various Communities.", 1922 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Steno notebook by William R. George, 1924 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Steno notebook by William R. George, 1925-1930 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Notebook by William R. George - "Social Doctor.", n.d. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Notebook by William R. George - "Social Sanitarium.", n.d. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Notebook by William R. George - "Part of story about Merle McReynolds.", n.d. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George; autobiographical notes on life of William R. George, 1905-1906 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George, 1908 (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George; marked Book I, Book II, Book III, 1908-1909 (Box 64, Folder 4-6)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George, 1911 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George, 1912 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George, 1917-1918 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Steno notebook by Esther George; one letter by James Garretson., 1931 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George, 1932 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George, 1933 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George; Phalanx and Adult Minor., 1933 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George; "Notes on Child Labor Amendment.", 1934 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Esther George; letters, 1934 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Steno notebook by Esther George with magazine articles about G.J.R., 1938-1939 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Steno notebook with "Notes on Articles on G.J.R. and Junior Municipality.", n.d. (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Steno notebook - "George Junior Republic.", n.d. (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Steno notebook by Esther George, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Eleanor M. George, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Eleanor M. George, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Eleanor M. George, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Pauline B. Brooks, 1911 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Edna Gelling, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Dictation by William R. George to Edna Gelling, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Dictation by C. Spencer Richardson to Pauline B. Brooks, 1912-1913 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Address book, 1888 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Address book, 1897 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Address book, 1907 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Address book, 1912 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Address book, 1915 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Address book, 1921 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Address book, 1921-1922 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Address book, 1925 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Address book, 1927-1929 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Address book, 1930-1931 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Address book, 1931-1932 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Address book, 1936 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Address books, 1930's (Box 65, Folder 13-15)
  - Address book, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Address books, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 17-18)
  - Address books, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 19-20)
  - Address books, 1942 (Box 65, Folder 21-22)
  - Address book, 1943 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Address books, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 24-27)
  - Address book, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Address book, 1946 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Address book, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Address book, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Address book, 1951 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Address book, 1952-1955 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Address book, 1954-1957 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Address book, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Address books, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 36-40)
  - Guest book, 1897-1899 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Guest book, 1897-1902 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Guest book, 1902-1903 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Guest book, 1905-1911 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Guest book, 1912-1923 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Guest book, 1922-1941 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Guest book, 1926 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Guest book, 1946-1948 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Citizen Senate Records, 1895-1896 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Citizen Senate Records, 1896 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Library Record, 1902-1903 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Police Record, 1906-1913 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Records of advertisements in "Junior Citizen.", 1900 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Records of Executive Committee, 1903-1906 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Library Record, 1907-1908 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Library Record, 1908-1911 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Library Record, 1911-1914 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Record, Clerk of Court, 1922-1923 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Jail Record, 1911-1915 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Record of Citizens' Jobs and Payments, 1913-1915 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Record of Citizens' Jobs and Payments, 1922 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Hospital Record, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - List of G.J.R. citizens, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - List of G.J.R. citizens, 1895-1908 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - List of G.J.R. citizens, 1895-1914 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - List of G.J.R. citizens, 1895-1926 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - List of G.J.R. citizens, 1895-1927 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - List of G.J.R. citizens, 1896-1927 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - List of G.J.R. citizens, 1908-1927 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Annotated calendar of Eleanor B. George., 1908 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Annotated calendar of Esther B. George, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Annotated calendar of Esther B. George, 1910 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Annotated calendar of Esther B. George, 1911 (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
  - Annotated calendar of Esther B. George, 1912 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Excerpts from diary of William R. George., 1907-1923 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Small handwritten and typescript pages, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - School notebook of W.H. Brewster, 1876 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - School notebook of William R. George, 1881 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - School notebook of Esther I. Brewster, 1890-1896 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - School notebook of William R. George, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Early schoolwork of William R. George, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - School notebook of Charles W. Brewster, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Autograph book of William R. George, 1881-1882 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Autograph book of Esther B. George, 1886-1891 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Book naming William R. George as member of Luther Burbank Society, 1907 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Journal kept by Merle McReynolds, 1913 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Sunday school record kept by P.A. Shortwell., 1913-1914 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Autograph book of Evelyn Reglin (Alton)., 1925 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - George Junior Republic Papers: Bridal book of Edith George Freeborn, 1930 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Memorial book for Esther B. George, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Business identification book used by J.F. George, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Small volume of recipes kept by Esther Brewster (George)., n.d. (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Book written by Mrs. J.F. George about prospective chapel on Baker State, G.J.R., n.d. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Book of songs; property of Richard M. Schell, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Small book belonging to Esther T. Brewster (George)., n.d. (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Small volume of unidentified handwriting, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - "G.J.R. Scrapbook," volume 1., 1891-1896 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - "G.J.R. Scrapbook," volume 2., 1896-1897 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - "G.J.R. Scrapbook," volume 3., 1898-1901 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - "G.J.R. Scrapbook," volume 4, with records of other republics, 1898-1900 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook about G.J.R., 1895-1912 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook presented to J.G. Smith by S.D. Miller, about G.J.R., 1896-1898 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook presented to J.G. Smith by S.D. Miller, about G.J.R., 1898-1900 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook presented to J.G. Smith by S.D. Miller, about G.J.R., 1897-1900 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook from G.J.R., 1902-1911 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook about G.J.R., 1908-1911 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook by Mrs. J.F. George of G.J.R. and George family, 1908-1911 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook by "Sister Betty" about G.J.R., 1908-1936 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook from G.J.R., 1909-1912 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook from G.J.R., 1912-1913 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook from G.J.R., about Junior Municipality and other junior republics., 1913-1914 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook from G.J.R., 1913-1914 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook from G.J.R. about other junior republics, 1914 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of meetings of Board of Trustees and Executive Committee of G.J.R., 1915-1925 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook concerning Child Labor Amendment, 1924-1925 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - G.J.R. scrapbook by Jack London, 1910-1940 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Book of clippings on Cortland Junior Municipality and Child Labor Amendment, 1933-1935 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Book of photographs of Esther George and others; presented to Esther George by Herman Deutschbein, 1960 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - G.J.R. scrapbook by Mr. and Mrs. Richard Catlin., 1960-1970 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook by Mary B. George (ca.1863- 1926)., n.d. (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Series IV. Miscellaneous
  - Typescript play, various handwritten and typescript testimonials to William R. George, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Songs and poems about G.J.R., William R. George, and Esther George, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous manuscripts related to G.J.R., n.d. (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous manuscripts about William R. George, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous manuscripts about G.J.R., n.d. (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Hunt School student essays, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Bookkeeping models, ca.1871 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - George Junior Republic - 90th Anniversary (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Columbus Army Flying School graduation program, 1944 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - "King Coal" postcard (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - 3 Civil War covers (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Series V. Printed Material
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1897-1900 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1901-1906 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1907-1909 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Junior Republic Principles and Bulletins by William R. George, 1909 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1910-1912 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1913-1920 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1921-1930 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1936-1939 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1940-1941 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1942-1947 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1948-1949 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1950-1955 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1956-1959 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1960 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1961 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1962 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1965-1970 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1970-1975 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., 1976-1984 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., n.d. (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Booklets and pamphlets about G.J.R., n.d. (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - G.J.R. Annual Reports, 1895-1909 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - G.J.R. Annual Reports, 1910-1975 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Christ Chapel (G.J.R.) memorial service programs, 1936-1984 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Hunt School (G.J.R.) Commencement programs, 1907-1959 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Hunt School (G.J.R.) Commencement programs, 1960-1984 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Hunt School Yearbooks, 1909-1946 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Hunt School Yearbooks, 1947-1979 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - G.J.R. Award and Testimonial Certificates, 1908-1984 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Moonlight Cruise, 1949-1954 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Junior Republic Ball, 1959-1963 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Social Events, 1897-1982 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Parent's Day/Open House programs, 1960-1982 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - G.J.R. literary magazines, 1963-1972 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Single sheets on G.J.R./W.R.G, 1896-1910 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Single sheets on G.J.R./W.R.G., 1911-1931 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Single sheets on G.J.R./W.R.G., 1932-1949 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Single sheets on G.J.R./W.R.G., 1950-1955 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Single sheets on G.J.R./W.R.G., 1956-1970 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Single sheets on G.J.R./W.R.G., n.d. (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlets and booklets mentioning G.J.R./W.R.G., 1899-1911 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - "Tourists' Telegraphic Code" book, 1920 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Bound Volumes
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1898-1899 (Volume 1)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1899-1900 (Volume 2)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1900-1901 (Volume 3)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1901-1902 (Volume 4)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1902-1903 (Volume 5)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1903-1904 (Volume 6)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1904-1905 (Volume 7)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1905-1906 (Volume 8)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1906-1907 (Volume 9)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1907-1908 (Volume 10)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1908-1909 (Volume 11)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1909-1910 (Volume 12)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1910-1911 (Volume 13)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1911-1912 (Volume 14)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1912-1913 (Volume 15)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1913-1914 (Volume 16)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, 1915-1916 (Volume 17)
  - The Junior Citizen, 1925-1927 (Volume 18)
  - The Advocate, n.d. (Volume 19)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, vols. 4-5., n.d. (Volume 20)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, vols. 2-3., n.d. (Volume 21)
  - The Citizen, vol. 1., n.d. (Volume 22)
  - The Citizen, vol. 6., n.d. (Volume 23)
  - Junior Republic Citizen, vol. 1., n.d. (Volume 24)
  - Pamphlets & Booklets mentioning G.J.R./W.R.G., 1931-1970 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets & Booklets mentioning G.J.R./W.R.G., 1971-1978, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Single sheets mentioning G.J.R./W.R.G., 1896-1914 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Single sheets mentioning G.J.R./W.R.G., 1915-1930 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Single sheets mentioning G.J.R./W.R.G., 1931-1955 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Single sheets mentioning G.J.R./W.R.G., 1945-1984, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Activities & subjects of interest to W.R.G.; arranged topically (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Inauguration & Dedication programs (G.J.R.), 1909-1969 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Inauguration & Dedication programs (G.J.R.)., 1970-1982 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - G.J.R. Anniversary & Founders' Day programs, 1905-1950 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - G.J.R. Anniversary & Founders' Day programs, 1951-1982 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Christ Chapel programs, 1908-1962 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Christ Chapel programs, 1963-1984 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Christ Chapel bulletins, 1980-1981 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Christ Chapel bulletins, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - G.J.R. blank forms - financial, legal, administrative, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - G.J.R. blank forms - employment & misc., n.d. (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - G.J.R. blank forms - award certificates, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - G.J.R. announcements & notices, 1972-1980 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - G.J.R. Community Schedule, 1974-1981 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - G.J.R. memoranda, 1966-1974 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - G.J.R. memoranda, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - G.J.R. memoranda, 1976-1978 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - G.J.R. memoranda, 1979-1985 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - California Junior Republic - misc. printed material, 1908-1949 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - California Junior Republic - misc., 1950-1970, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. I., Apr. 1911-Mar. 1912 (Box 96, Folder 3)